

Losev EVGENYI
Front-end Developer / React JS

Belarus, Minsk

☑ ex-youjeen@mail.ru

© +375 33 697 50 85

SOCIAL

@YouJeen-ru

in @losev-evgeniy

₩ @evgeny.losev

@YouJeens

EDUCATION

Front-end React Developer

IT-Incubator 2021

Paramedic

MINSK STATE MEDICAL COLLEGE 2015-2018

SKILLS

- JavaScript / TypeScript
- React / React Hooks
- Redux / Redux-Thunk / Redux-Toolkit
- HTML5 / CSS3 / BEM
- Git / GitHub
- Rest API / HTTP / Axios

LANGUAGES

- English (Pre-Intermediate)
- Russian (Native)

PROFILE

I'm a front-end developer who has a results-focused attitude to creating SPA, using React(JS/TS), Redux.Throughout the year I have been striving to develop as a specialist.Experience in creating, maintaining and improving web applications from scratch. During development, I have acquired strong analytical and troubleshooting skills. I believe that I am a good team player with a strong ability to learn and adapt new skills to your needs. I am full of energy and , skills and willingness to learn any other technologies.In my spare time I also improve my English and develop apps for open-source.

EXPERIENCE

Front-end Developer | React JS

03.2021 - present | Freelance

- Creation of applications for technical specifications.
- Implementation of new functionality in projects: registration / authentication / pagination, etc.
- Improving performance using: React.memo, React.lazy, React.suspense.
- Checking the correctness of the code using Unit test.

React Developer (during the course)

03.2021 - 08.2021 | It-Incubator

Practical study of technologies: TypeScript, React, Redux / Thunk / Toolkit. Working with REST API. Analysis of technical specifications Development of SPA architecture. Work on internal projects in a team of 3 people.

1. Todo - Demo | Code

- -Creating SPA in React \ TypeScript \ Material UI \ Rest Api \ Unit test.
- -Using Redux as state management.

2. Simplex - Demo | Code

- -Chat in real-time on ChatEngine.io
- -Implemented registration and authentication Firebase.

3. Social Network - Code

- -Working an application with REST API. Parsing the Flux principle.
- -Storing data in Redux and local components

JavaScript Developer (during the course)

01.2021 - 02.2021 | Udemy

Creating a full application on your own framework.

1. Excel - Demo | Code

- -Learning JavaScript ES6+ in Practice. Working with Git.
- -Implementation of OOP in the app, parsing of the principle of SOLID.
- -DOM manipulation, state management. Routing and create new pages.

Front-end developer / HTML-coder (during the course)

10.2020 - 12.2020 | Glo Academy

Practical learning of the basics of HTML\CSS.

Semantic layout based on Figma layouts Basic JavaScript ES6+ , React.js.

1. Willberries - Demo | Code

- -Adaptive website layout, implementing simple ES6 validation
- -Product loading by working with Rest Api, product search on the site.

2. SpaceX - Demo | Code

- -Implementing SPA on class components.
- -Working with Rest Api by writing custom hooks. Content routing